Guide to the Rochambeau Papers and Rochambeau Family Cartographic Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Map Collection of the Vicomte de Rochambeau, 1702-1823; Series VI; 7; (17 boxes)
  - PRISONER IN ENGLAND
    - IK 336 Parts 1-4. A Map of the Kingdom of Ireland. (Box 27, Folder 552-555)
      1) Inscribed on map, part 1: IK/336
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 1: Carte/de l'Irlande/1e Flle. The label reads: A PARIS/Chez Lattré graveur ord. du Roi Rue St/Jacques vis à vis celle de la Parcheminerie
      Title and/or other information taken from map, part 1: A MAPP/OF THE KINGDOM OF/IRELAND/NEWLY CORRECTED & IMPROV'D By Actual Observations/Divided into its PROVINCES COUNTIES &BARONIES And Supply'd with many/Market Towns & other Places of Note Omitted in former Mapps with all the Principal Roads & the Distances from Place/to Place in Comon Reputed Miles by Inspection And wherein the Citys & Chief Towns, Arch=Bishopricks, & Bishopricks/Burroughs, Market Towns, Villages & Barracks, are Respectively distinguish'd by different Characters and the/Lakes Bogs Mountains Rivers Bridges Ferreys & Passes described with several other Additions/Alterations and Amendments Together with Plans of the Citys and Fortified Towns As Allso a Short/Description of the Kingdom By HENRY PRATT/To this map is added a large Index of the Measur'd Distances of ev'ry town from Dublin/of the Burroughs, Barracks, and Post Towns with Many other Improvements and Emendations/ [and] TABULA HIBERNIAE NOVIS/[continues to next map]
      Notes to map, part 1: This is the upper left quarter of the map. Linen-backed. Colored. 25 1/8 x 20 1/4 inches overall. 8 1/2 x 7 inches folded.
      2) Inscribed on label laid down on map 2: Irlande 2e flle. The label reads as above.
      Title and/or other information taken from map, part 2: [continued from previous map] SIMA ET EMENDATISSIMA
      Notes to map, part 2: This is the upper right quarter of the map. Linen-backed. Colored. 25 1/8 x 19 1/4 inches overall. 8 1/2 x 7 inches folded.
      3) Inscribed on label laid down on map 3: Irlande 3e flle. The label reads as above.
      Notes to map, part 3: This is the lower left quarter of the map. Linen-backed. Colored. 25 1/8 x 20 1/4 inches overall. 8 1/2 x 7 inches folded.
      4) Inscribed on label laid down on map 4: Irlande 4e flle. The label reads as above.
      Notes to map, part 4: This is the lower right quarter of the map. Linen-backed. Colored. 25 x 19 3/8 inches.
    - IK 280 Map of the States of Parma and Modena. Venice: P. Santini., 1779 (Box 27, Folder 556)
      Inscribed on map: IK/280.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Etats/de Parme/et de Modene
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/DES ETATS/DE PARME, ET/DE MODENE,/avec/LA PARTIE ORIENTALE DE LA RIVIERE/DE GENES/A VENISE/Par P. Santini 1779/Chez M Remon/dini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 18 11/16 x 25 inches overall. 7 3/4 x 5 1/4 inches folded.
    - IK 286 City of Milan., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 557)
      Inscribed on map: IK/286
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: citta/di milano
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CITTA DI MILANO/[and] Si vende presso Matteo Margaillan Libraro/ sotto il Coperto de Figini
      Notes: Linen-backed. Uncolored. 24 x 23 1/4 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 287 New map of Crema. Venice: P. Santini., 1779 (Box 27, Folder 558)
      Inscribed on map: IK/287
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Territoire/de Crema.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: NOUVELLE CARTE/DU/TERRITOIRE DE CREME/Suivant le Plan/dressé sur les lieux/A VENISE/Par P. Santini 1779./Chez Mr. Remondini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 21 5/8 x 17 3/4 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 274 Map of Friuli., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 559)
      Inscribed on map: IK/274
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Carte/du Frioul Venitien,/Des Comtés de Gorizia, de/Gradisca, et du district de Trieste.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: IL FRIULI/ colle/CONTEE DI GORIZIA, GRADISCA E DISTRETTO DI/TRIESTE/IN VENEZIA
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 19 3/4 x 26 1/4 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches, folded.
    - IK 273 State of the House of Austria in Italy After the Treaty of Peace of Campo Formio. Bassano: Remondini., 1798 (Box 27, Folder 560)
      Inscribed on map: IK/273
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Ligne de l'armistice/ conclu entre les armées/Françaises et Imperiales/en Italie./an.9/[There is another label laid down on the outside of this map, but it is not inscribed.]
      Title and/or other information taken from map: ÉTAT/DE LA MAISON D'AUTRICHE/EN ITALIE/D'après le Traité de Paix/de Campo Formio près d'Udine,/du 17 Octobre 1797./Dressé sur les meilleures Cartes/BASSANO 1798/Chez Remondini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 19 3/4 x 26 1/2 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 269 Map of Italy by Brion. Paris: Desnos., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 561)
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: IK/269 [and] Carte Itineraire/des Routes d'Italie./[and] par Brion
      Circular Label laid down on map reads: a Paris/Chez Vignon Marchand/de Cartes de Géographe,/rue Dauphine vis-à-vis/ celle d'Anjou.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/D' ITALIE,/Assujettie/aux Observations Astronomiques/et Aux Itnéraires./Comprenant/Toutes les grandes Routes/qui traversent les différens Etats de cette Région,/et s'étendent jusques dans la Sicile;/avec les distances par Postes./Par M. BRION Ingenieur-Géographe/A PARIS/Chez le CN. DESNOS rue St. Jacques au Globe.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 30 5/16 x 34 9/16 inches overall. 7 3/4 x 5 1/4 inches folded.
    - IK 268 Map Showing the March of the French Army in Germany and Italy, by P. G. Chanlaire. Paris. (Box 27, Folder 562)
      Inscribed on map: 22/50
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Theatre de la Guerre/ en Italie/[and] IK/268.
      Circular label laid down on map Reads: a Paris/Chez Vignon Marchand/de Cartes de Géographie,/rue Dauphine vis-à-vis/ celle d'Anjou.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE ITINÉRAIRE INDIQUANT LA MARCHE DES ARMÉES FRANCAISES EN ALLEMAGNE ET EN ITALIE:/Faisant suitte à la Carte en 8. Feuilles de L. CAPITAINE 1er. Ingénr de la Carte de France./Par P. G. Chanlaire, associé à l'entreprise de la même Carte et l'un des Auteurs de l'Atlas National./A Paris au Dépôt de Géographie, Rue Geoffroy Langevin No. 328./ [and] Partie Méridle 1ere Feuille.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 32 7/8 x 23 1/4 inches overall. 8 1/2 x 6 inches folded.
    - IK 300 Topographical map of the City of Genoa., 1789 (Box 28, Folder 563)
      Inscribed on map: IK/300.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Plan de/Genes.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: TOPOGRAFIA DEL PORTO, E/CITTA DI GENOVA/nel solo ristretto delle sue Mura Vecchie,/coll'indicazione delle Chiese, e luoghi principali/DEDICATA A SUA ECCELLENZA/IL SIG. GEROLAMO DURAZZO/PATRIZIO GENOVESE/Dal suo Umo. e Obbo. servie/ Ivone Gravier Libraro in Genova/[and] Delineata da Giacomo Bruschi Capno. Ingegniere 1789
      Notes: Linen-backed. Uncolored. 16 7/8 x 23 3/8 inches overall. 8 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 303 Tyrol by Robert. Venice: P. Santini., 1778 (Box 28, Folder 564)
      Inscribed on map: IK/303.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Le Tyrol.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: LE TYROL/ sous le nom duquel l'on comprend/LE COMTÉ DE TYROL,/les Comtés annèxes de/BREGENTZ, FELDKIRCK, MONFORT,/PLUDENTZ, &c./et les Evêchés de/TRENTE, ET DE BRIXEN,/PAR LE Sr. ROBERT/A VENISE/Par P. Santini 1778./Chez Mr. Remondini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 19 x 21 1/2 inches overall. 6 1/2 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 294 The territory of Verona. Venice: P. Santini., 1776 (Box 28, Folder 565)
      Inscribed on map:IK/294
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Territoire/de Verone.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: LE/ TERRITOIRE/DE/VERONE/dressé sur les/meilleures Cartes./A VENISE/Par P. Santini 1776./Chez Mr. Remondini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 18 7/8 x 22 5/16 inches overall. 6 1/2 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 292 City and Territory of Turin. Fratelli Reycend & Co. (Box 28, Folder 566)
      Inscribed on map: IK/292/[and] Citta di Torino.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CITTA E TERRITORIO DI TORINO/[and] Delineata da Carlo Randon/Regio Architetto/Intagliata da Ant. M. Stagnon/Incisore de Sigilli di S.M./Si vende dalli Fratelli Reycends/e Compagnia Librari al Cantone/di Contrada nuova
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 24 3/16 x 19 1/4 inches overall. 8 1/2 x 6 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 291 Mantua and Environs., 1796 (Box 28, Folder 567)
      Inscribed on map: IK/291.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Carte/de Mantoue et des/attaques des Français/en 1796. --
      Title and/or other information taken from map: MANTOVA/E SUO CIRCONDARIO/con la Dichiarazione delle Opere d' Assedio/fatte dall'Armata FRANCESE in Luglio del 1796
      Notes: Linen-backed. Uncolored. 23 1/8 x 20 5/8 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/4 inches folded.
    - IK 290 Map of Padua. Venice: P. Santini., 1776 (Box 28, Folder 568)
      Inscribed on map: IK/290.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Carte/du Padouan, du/ Dogado, Et du/Vicentin.--
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE DU/ PADOUAN,/DU DOGADO,/et de la plus grande partie/DU VICENTIN,/Dressée sur celle/DU Sr. PAUL BARTHELEMI/ CLARICI./A VENISE/Par P. Santini 1776./Chez M Remondini.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 19 x 26 7/16 inches overall. 6 1/2 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 288 Plan of Mantua, by Pinchetty., 1800 (Box 28, Folder 569)
      Inscribed on map: IK/288.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Plan des/attaques faittes par/les Français et Les-/autrichiens Sur La ville/ de Mantoue. - par Pinchetty./[and] 1796-1799.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: Piano della Citta'di Mantova, e suoi Contorni/[and] Milano 1800./ Pinchetti Geogfo.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 27 7/8 x 22 3/4 inches overall. 7 3/4 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
  - CENTRAL EUROPEAN CAMPAIGNS
    - IK 258 Map of Hungary and Transylvania. Weimar., 1804 (Box 28, Folder 570)
      Originally cased in a patterned board sleeve. See also: Oversize Sleeve Boxes, box 52.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CHARTE/von/ UNGARN, SIEBENBÜRGEN/u.s.f./Nach den bewährtesten Hülfsmitteln neu entworfen/und gezeichnet/von/F. GÖTZE./ Weimar/Im Verlage des Geograph. Instituts/1804.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 17 1/8 x 24 1/8 inches overall. 8 1/4 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 128 The Low Countries., 1794 (Box 28, Folder 571)
      Inscribed on map: IK/128/[and] Pays-Bas/1794
      Title and/or other information taken from map: TABLEAU/DES PAYS-BAS/INDIQUANT/LES ROUTES ET DISTANCES/DE PARIS/AUX VILLES PRINCIPALES/DES XVII PROVINCES/Et des Etats Limitrophes/Par AE-O [rest illegible] Ing. Géog./En 1794. [and] Gravée par Trébuchet
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 15 5/16 x 13 15/16 inches overall. 4 3/4 x 4 inches folded.
    - IK 267 Table of the Map of the Austrian Lowlands. (Box 28, Folder 572)
      Map tab inscription: No. 1/l'Explication
      Inscribed on map: IK/267.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: No. 1/L'explication de la Carte/et des Signes relatifs aux objets qu'elle représente/[and] Pays Bas/autrichiens.
      Circular label laid down on map reads: a Paris/Chez Vignon Marchand/de Cartes de Géographie,/rue Dauphine vis-à-vis/ celle d'Anjou.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: EXPLICATION/ DE LA NOUVELLE CARTE CHOROGRAPHIQUE DES PAYS-BAS AUTRICHIENS, Y COMPRIS/LES PRINCIPAUTÉS DE LIEGE ET DE STAVELOT./[and] Gravée par L. A. Dupuis
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 23 5/8 x 19 11/16 inches overall. 8 x 5 inches folded.
    - IK 308 Basel., n.d. (Box 28, Folder 573)
      Map tab inscription: No. 165/Basle
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: No. 165. flle/70/ Basle/[and] IK/308.
      Circular label laid down on map reads: a Paris/Chez Vignon Marchand/de Cartes de Géographie/rue Dauphine vis-à-vis/ celle d'Anjou.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: Chalmandrier Sculp
      Notes: Linen-backed. Uncolored. 23 1/2 x 30 1/2 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/4 inches folded.
    - IK 307 Switzerland Divided into 13 Cantons by Robert de Vaugondy. (Box 28, Folder 574)
      Inscribed on map: IK/307
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Carte de/la Suisse/par Vaugondy.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: LA SUISSE/ divisee/en treize CANTONS/[and] Redigêe/par ROBERT de/ UAUGONDI d'apres/les meilleurs/auteurs et sur les/ Observations faites/par lui meme sur/les lieux/Grave Par F. Bordiga
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 20 13/16 x 26 1/8 inches overall. 7 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 217 Swabia. Augsburg: J. Walch., 1803
      Inscribed on map: Wurtemberg. [this has been crossed out]/ [and] IK/217./[and] Souabe
      Title and/or other information taken from map: DER/ SCHWAEBISCHE/KREIS./nach dessen neuen Sakularisationen/ und Entschädigungen entworfen./Augsburg/Zufinden bey Joh. Walch/1803.
      Notes: Colored. 22 3/16 x 26 3/4 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Boxes, box 50, folder 793.
    - IK 346 The Borders of Austria, Russia and the Ottoman Empire., 1785 (Box 29, Folder 575)
      Inscribed on map: IK/346/[and] Parties limitrophes/De l'autriche, de la/Russie et de L'Empire/Ottoman./par Rhode.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: Partes confines/TRIUM MAGNORUM IMPERIORUM/AUSTRIACI RUSSICI/et/ OSMANICI/Foliis VI comprehensa/ex novissimis observationibus, dimensionibus/optimisque tabulis geographicis descriptae/AVSP.ACAD.REG.SCIENT. et ELEG.LITT./a I.C. Rhode Acad. suprad. Geogr./Anno MDCCLXXXV.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 37 3/4 x 53 ll/16 inches overall. 9 3/4 x 6 inches folded.
    - IK 304 Parts 1-6. Map of Tyrol., n.d. (Box 29, Folder 576-581)
      1) Inscribed on map, part 1: IK/304.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 1: Carte/du Tyrol./Fussen. (Tussen ?)/Kempten.-/1.
      Notes to map, part 1: Stamped in red on map: DEPOT/ GENERAL/DE LA/GUERRE. This is the upper left section (1/6th) of the map. Linen-backed. Uncolored. 24 x 34 1/4 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
      2) Inscribed on label laid down on map 2: Carte/du Tyrol./Husstein - 2.
      Notes to map, part 2: Same stamp appears on this map. This is the upper right section (1/6th) of the map. Linen- backed. Uncolored. 23 13/16 x 34 1/4 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
      3) Inscribed on label laid down on map 3: Carte/du Tyrol./Glurens.-3.
      Notes to map, part 3: Same stamp appears on this map. This is the center left section (1/6th) of the map. Linen- backed. Uncolored. 23 3/4 x 34 1/8 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
      4) Inscribed on label laid down on map 4: Carte/du Tyrol./Lienz.-/4.
      Notes to map, part 4: Same stamp appears on this map. This is the center right section (1/6th) of the map. Linen- backed. Uncolored. 23 1/2 x 34 3/8 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/4 inches folded.
      5) Inscribed on label laid down on map 5: Carte/du Tyrol./Trento-/5.
      Notes to map, part 5: Same stamp appears on this map. This is the lower left section (1/6th) of the map. Linen- backed. Uncolored. 23 1/2 x 34 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
      6) Inscribed on label laid down on map 6: Carte/du Tyrol./Feltre- 6./Tableau d'assemblage-
      Title and/or other information taken from map, part 6: TABLEAU D'ASSEMBLAGE/des six Feuilles/de la Carte du Tyrol
      Notes to map, part 6: Same stamp appears on this map. This is the lower right section (1/6th) of the map. Linen- backed. Uncolored. 23 3/8 x 34 1/8 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 345 Russia and Turkey. Paris. (Box 29, Folder 582)
      Inscribed on map: IK/345/[and] Russie et Turquie.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/de la/ RUSSIE D'EUROPE/ET DE LA/TURQUIE/Théâtre de la Guerre en Orient./A. LOGEROT, Quai des Augustins No. 55./Paris./ 1854/[and] Extrait de la grande Carte d'Europe, dressée par BRUÉ./[and] Imp. Lemercier, Paris.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 38 x 25 13/16 inches overall. 9 3/4 x 6 1/2 inches folded.
  - FRENCH AND EUROPEAN CAMPAIGNS
    - IK 147 France by Perrier. Paris: Basset., [1801 or 1802] (Box 30, Folder 583)
      Inscribed on map: France/en 108 depts/[and] IK/147
      Title and/or other information taken from map: TABLEAU,/ DE LA FRANCE,/Dressé par Brion;/DIVISÉ EN 108 DÉPARTEMENS/ ET EN PRÉFECTURES ET SOUS-PRÉFECTURES./par Perrier/A Paris, chez Basset Md d'Estampes et Fabriquant de/Papiers Peints, Rue Jacques No. 670/An X.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 21 1/4 x 30 9/16 inches overall. 8 x 5 1/2 inches folded.
    - IK 150 Europe. Homann Erben., n.d. (Box 30, Folder 584)
      Inscribed on map: Europe/[and] IK/150
      Title and/or other information taken from map: EVROPA/In partes su as X Metho-/dicas a primariis regnis deno/ minatas/divisa/secundum fidem recentissimarum/ observationum Mathematicarum/et Historicarum,/et exhibita/ secundum legitimas projecti/onis Stereographicae legre/à IOH. MATTH. HASIO/Math. P. P. O./Impensus facientibus/ HAEREDIGVS HOMANIANIS./Cum Priv./Sac. Caes/Majest/Grat./ [and] I.C. Reinsperger Sculpsit.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 37 5/8 x 44 1/2 inches overall. 9 1/2 x 5 3/4 inches folded.
    - IK 34 Europe by J. B. de Bouge., 1803 (Box 30, Folder 585)
      Originally cased in a blue board sleeve. See also: Oversize Sleeve Boxes, box 52.
      Inscribed on map Proper: IK/34.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/DE L'EUROPE/Dediée/A SON ALTESSE ROYALE MONSEIGNEUR/CHARLES LOUIS ARCHIDUC D'AUTRICHE,/PRINCE ROYAL DE HONGRIE, ET DE BOHÉME,/Chevalier de la Toison d'or, Grand-Croix de l'ordre militaire/de Marie Thérése./GÉNÉRAL FELD-MARÉCHAL DES ARMÉES DU ST. EMPIRE ROMAIN/Général d'Artillerie, de Celles Impériales et Royales./Colonel propriétaire d'un Regiment d'Infanterie/au Service de S. M. l'Empereur et Roi/Et Commandant Général des Armées/du St. Empire et de celles Impériales et Royales./GRAND-MAITRE DE L'ORDRE TEUTONIQUE/ etc. etc. etc./Par son trés humble/et trés respectueux Serviteur/I. B. De Bouge/Ingenieur Géographe./Pensionné de/Sa M: Pruss/1803.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 84 1/2 x 82 1/2 inches overall. 14 x 9 inches folded.
  - SPANISH AND PORTUGESE CAMPAIGNS
    - IK 311 Parts 1-6. Spain and Portugal. Paris: P. G. Chanlaire. (Box 30, Folder 586-591)
      Originally cased together in linen covered board sleeve. See also: Oversize Sleeve Boxes, box 52. All maps 7 x 6 1/2 inches folded.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 1: l/Galicie./ [and] IK/311.
      Notes to map, part 1: This is the upper left section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 5/8 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 2: 2/Navarre- Biscaye-/Burgos./[and] 2
      Notes to map, part 2: This is the upper middle section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 1/2 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 3: 3/Catalogne./ [and] 3
      Notes to map, part 3: This is the upper right section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 1/2 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 4: 4./Portugal./ [and] 4
      Notes to map, part 4: This is the center left section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 1/2 x 17 7/16 inches.
    - IK 311 Parts 7-9. Spain and Portugal. Paris: P. G. Chanlaire. (Box 31, Folder 592-594)
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 5: 5./Tolède- Cuença./[and] 5
      Notes to map, part 5: This is the center middle section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 9/16 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 6: 6./Valence- IS- Ma-/jorque, etc. -/[and] 6
      Notes to map, part 6: This is the center right section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 1/2 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 7: 7./Séville.
      Notes to map, part 7: This is the lower left section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 7/16 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 8: 8./Grenade- Cordoue.
      Notes to map, part 8: This is the lower middle section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 7/16 x 17 5/16 inches.
      Inscribed on label laid down on map 9: 9/Titre. [and]/9
      Title and/or other information taken from map, part 9: CARTE/D'ESPAGNE ET DE PORTUGAL/EN NEUF FEUILLES/Par E. MENTELLE Membre de l'Institut National des Sciences/Et P. G. CHANLAIRE l'un des Auteurs de l'Atlas National./A PARIS/ Chez les Auteurs/P. G. Chanlaire, Rue Geoffroy-Langevin; No. 7./Et E. Mentelle, Rue Mazarine No. 52
      Notes to map, part 9: This is the lower right section of the map. There are three sections of three pieces each. Linen-backed. Colored. 13 5/8 x 17 3/8 inches.
    - IK 313 Spain by N. Bailleul le jeune. Lyon: Daudet., 1762 (Box 31, Folder 595)
      Inscribed on map: IK/313./[and] Espagne./par Bailleul
      Inscribed on label laid down on map: Carte piquée d'epingles pour/marquer la campagne de Madrid/1807-1808
      Title and/or other information taken from map: L'ESPAGNE/ Divisée en tous ses Royaumes et Principautés/telle qu'elle est possedée par sa Majesté Catholique/FERDINAND VI. ROY D'ESPAGNE ET DES INDES/DÉDIÉE/A MESSIRE CAMILLE PERRICHON/ Ancien Prevôt des Marchands et Commandant/de la Ville de Lyon./Chevalier de l'Ordre du Roy, Conseiller d'Etat Ord./Par son tres humble et tres/Obeissant Serviteur/N. BAILLEUL/le jeune/en 1762/[and] A Lyon chez Daudet rue Merciere
      Notes: This map has stick pins that indicate the march of Napoleon on Madrid. Linen-backed. Colored. 21 5/8 x 30 inches overall. 8 x 6 inches folded.
    - IK 312 Map of Spain and Portugal. Paris., 1823
      Inscribed on map: IK/312./[and] Espagne et Portugal./[and] Espagne et Portugal/1823.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: Carte/DES ROYAUMES/D'ESPAGNE ET DE PORTUGAL/OU L'ON A MARQUE LES ROUTES DE POSTE./Dressée d'après les dernieres Observations Astronomique/et les nouvelles Cartes espagnoles gravées ou manuscrites/1823/Revue et Augmentée/[and] Gravé par E. Collin, rue de la Harpe No. 45.
      Notes: Colored. 33 1/2 x 43 1/2 inches.
      SEE: Oversize Rolled Maps, folder 903.
    - IK 314 Portugal. Paris: Julien., 1762 (Box 31, Folder 596)
      Inscribed on map: IK/314/[and] Portugal/[and] carte du portugal
      Title and/or other information taken from map: LE ROYAUME/ DE PORTUGAL/Divisé/EN CINQ GRANDES PROVINCES/et Subdivisé en plusieurs Territoires/Avec/LE ROYAUME DES ALGRAVES./LE STRAMADOVRA ESPAGNOL/et partie d'Andalousie/Dressé sur les Memoires les plus Nouveaux/et Dedié/A SA MAJESTÉ TRES CHRETIENE/LOUIS LE GRAND/Par son tres-humble et tres-obeissant/serviteur et fidel sujet I. B. Nolin./A PARIS/Chez le Sr. Julien a l'Hotel/de Soubise./Avec Privilege du Roi./du 25 Janvier 1762.
      Notes: Linen-backed. Colored. 25 5/8 x 18 3/4 inches overall. 6 1/2 x 5 inches folded.
    - IK 148 States and Kingdoms Situated on the Mediterranean.
      Inscribed on map: Etats/situés sur la Méditerranie/[and] IK/148.
      Title and/or other information taken from map: CARTE/Ou l'on voit la position des/PRINCIPAUX ROYAUMES ET ETATS,/ qui environnoient/LA MEDITERRANÉE,/Lorsque les Romains commence-/=rent leurs Guerres au dela de/L'ITALIE./[and] Picquet Sculpt.